WWW.52HALFCD.COM
时代影视论坛 荣誉出品
影片压制&字幕制作：liubinqing
到什么地方去呀？
Go to where go to ah?
我头一次来香港
I first come to Hong Kong
请你送我到清水道一三一四地段
Please send me to the clear water way 1314 districts
朋友，一三一四地段在什么地方？
Friend, 1314 district's wheres?
在那边
Over there
你知道郭南昌这个人住在哪儿吗？
Do you know where this person of Guo Nan Chang lives?
前面没有房子，是坟地呀
There being before no house is a graveyard
啊？
?
怎么回事呀？
What is the row ah?
车子开不过去了
The car opens however go to
你自己下来走过去吧，二十块
Yourself come down to walk over, 20 piece
快点，快点
Hurry, hurry
我还要做生意呢
Do I still need to do business
一三一四地段怎么在这种地方？
1314 districts how in this kind of place?
小姐
Young lady
只有你一个人呀？
Only have your a person?
我
I
你们想干什么？
Do you want to do what?
不干什么，想亲热亲热
Not stem what, think to be warm and affectionate
救命啊…
Help …
反抗也没用
Resist also useless
救命啊…
Help …
你们干什么？
What are you dry?
快，走
Walk quickly
快走，不然我叫警察来抓你们
Walk quickly, otherwise I call the police come to grasp you
马上滚，滚蛋，快滚，滚
Roll right away, fuck off, roll quickly, roll
不要紧吧？
Unimportant?
谢谢你救了我
Thanked you to save me
我刚到这个地方来，真可怕
I just got to this place, barf city
你是外地来的吗？
Are you an other parts of country to come?
我刚从台湾来的
I just came from Taiwan
快上车吧
Get on the car quickly
你来找你妹妹的？
You to seek your younger sister?
是的，有个叫郭南昌的
There is calling Guo Nan Chang yes of
说把我妹妹带到香港来唱歌
Say taking my younger sister to Hong Kong to sing a song
来了以后就没有消息了
Come later have no news
你妹妹会唱歌呀？
Will your younger sister sing a song?
会，在台北我们一起唱的
Meeting, we sing together in Taipei
我们是用金丝雀姐妹的名字登台的
We are the names used canary sister to go on stage
金丝雀姐妹？
Canary sister?
我好像听说过
I seemed to once hear
我们圈子里的人
Our person of turn son inside
都说你们的歌唱得很好
All say your to sing very good
哪里，过奖了
Where, overpraise
请问你是…
Excuse me, you is …
我叫王德生，是个作曲的
I call Wang De to living, is 1 to compose
在一家唱片公司里工作
Work in a record company
香港并不大
Hong Kong isn't big
我想一定可以找到你妹妹的
I think to definitely find out your younger sister
我来帮你找好了
I to seek for you
谢谢你
Thank you
还没请教你贵姓？
Haven't asked what is your surname?
我叫尤淑文
I call You Shu Wen
尤小姐，你要到哪里去呀？
Ms. You, you want where go to?
我也不知道什么地方好
I don't know as well where good
你知不知道有什么地方
You know not to know to have where
有比较便宜的公寓可以租的呀？
Have cheaper apartment can rent of ah?
那就到我的公寓里来吧
That apartment that is me inside come
啊？
?
不，你不要担心
Not, you don't want to worry
我们七楼那家女子公寓
We the seventh floor that woman apartment
里面也有歌声
The inside also has singing
你要找妹妹也比较方便一点
You have to seek a younger sister also more convenience a point
真谢谢你
Really thank you
来
Come
就是这儿
Is here
美雅公寓呀
Beautiful graceful apartment
全是漂亮小姐
Whole is beautiful young lady
王先生
Mr. Wang
小丁，可以考黑带了吧？
Small D, can test black take?
光只是看书是不行
Light's just reading a book is to don't go
我想找个对手来练习练习
I want to seek an opponent to practice a practice
偏偏这儿的房客都是小姐
It happened that all of tenants here are young ladies
陈太太在不在？
Mrs. Chen at not at?
在
At
妈咪，六楼的王先生来找你
Mummy, Mr. Wang of the sixth floors comes to seek you
陈太太
Mrs. Chen
Tommy常常给你添麻烦
Tommy usually troubles you
找我有什么指教吗？
Seek I have what advise?
我介绍位房客来给你
I introduce a tenant to come to you
你好
How do you do
是你的女朋友？
The girl friend that is you?
不，她是从台湾来找她妹妹的
Not, she seeks her younger sister from Taiwan
她人很好
Her person is very good
刚刚7号房倒是空着
Just No.7 building's pouring be getting empty
不过我先告诉你
However I tell you first
我们这家公寓是男宾止步
We this apartment is a male guest to halt
男人不准进来的
The man prohibits incoming
您也不能例外
You also not ability exception
我知道，我知道
I know that I know
行李在这儿
The baggage is here
给我吧
Give me
谢谢你，王先生
Thank you, Mr. Wang
哪里，哪里
Where, where
我住六楼，就在你房间的下面
I live the sixth floors, the underneath in your room
有什么事情，你叫我好了
What is up, you call me good
你想爬上来呀？
Do you want to climb to come up?
我不是那种人，你放心
I ain't that kind of people, you trust
放心？把内衣三角裤晾在窗外
Trust?Chase underwear panties the Liang is outside the window
一会儿就不见了
In a short while be missing
有男人的地方就是不能放心
The place with a man is to can not trust
拜拜…
Worship …
请进来吧
Please come in
你叫什么名字？
What name do you call?
我叫尤淑文
I call You Shu Wen
今年几岁呀？
How old this year?
二十岁
20 years old
Tommy，为什么进来？
Tommy why comes in?
我拿箱子嘛
I take a box
不行，你是男人，给我出去
Don't go, you are a man and go out for me
你看看
You see
这个地方连我儿子都不能进来
This place's connecting my sons can not come in
你也休想带男朋友进来
You also don't think that to take boyfriend to come in
你的职业是…
You of occupation is …
目前还没有，我刚刚到香港来
So far didn't°yet, I just got to Hong Kong
房租两百块，你负担得了吗？
The rent is 200 pieces, can you bear?
可以的
Can of
那我带你去看房间
That I take you see room
你要出去呀？
Do you want to go out?
走吧
Leave
我来跟你们介绍
I come to introduce with you
这位是新搬来的房客
This is the lately- moved tenant
她住在7号房
She lives building in the No.7
这位Erin是在咖啡店做事的
This Erin works in the cafe
就在弥敦道，有空请来喝茶
In the way of Mi Dun, free please to drink tea
这是马琪，是在美容院工作的
This is Ma Qi and work in the beauty salon
你要想洗头呀，可以到我们店里来
You have to want to shampoo ah, can go to inside in our store
谢谢
Thank
陈太太，快来
Mrs. Chen come quickly
什么事？什么事？
What matter?What matter?
你来看
You to see
你看…
You see …
他们在干什么？
They at dry what?
你们干什么？
What are you dry?
居然偷人家的内衣裤
The underwear that incredibly has an affair with man a house
我报警去了
I reported to the police to go to
你们再这样，我绝不放过你们的
You again so, I in no case pass you
岂有此理，不要脸
How could such a thing be possible, shameless
这些男人就好像疯了一样
These men seem to be crazy
那些男人，你要特别的小心
Those men, you want special caution
罗娜，这是你隔壁的新房客
Luo Nuo, this is the new tenant of your next door
尤小姐
Ms. You
Hello
你好
How do you do
她是在珠宝店里做事的
She works in the jewelry shop
这是你的房间
This room that is you
就是这一间了
Is this
把衣服脱下来
Strip off clothes
脱衣服？
Does the undressing take?
让我看看你是不是个女人
Show me you isn't a women
你看我这个样子就应该知道了
You see my this appearance and then should know
不行，不行
Don't go, don't go
以前住在这儿的舞女
The dance-hostess that lived here before
把男朋友带进来
Take boyfriend to come in
后来我检查她的内衣才发现了
Afterwards I checked her underwear and just discovered
不要这样子嘛
Don't like this
不行，一定要检查，没有办法了
Don't go, must check, have no way
真是莫名其妙
Is really puzzling
的确是个女人
Really is a women
对不起，你把房间整理好了
Execuse me, you tidied up room
我给你介绍其他的房客
I introduce other tenants for you
Hello，George
Hello, George
昨天晚上玩得真痛快
Had fun last night really to heart's content
我刚起床耶
I just got up
昨晚上我还梦见你呢
Ascended me to still dream you last night
我还没吃中饭
I haven't had lunch
你请我吃，好不好？
You invite me to eat, not very good?
吃完了饭再去兜兜风
Finished eating rice then go for a ride
然后一起到夜总会去
Then arrive night club together
你说，好不好？
You say that not very good?
佐治，你已经有了我
The Zuo cures, you have already had me
还跟这种黄毛丫头搞什么鬼？
Still make with this kind of witless young girl what ghost?
你干什么？是老板打给我的
What are you dry?Is a boss to call my
去你的，你不要忘了
Go to you of, you didn't want to forget
是我把你介绍到夜总会去的
Is that I introduce you to the night club to go
是又怎么样？
BE how again?
我又年轻，又漂亮
I am again young, again beautiful
歌也比你唱得好
The song also sings well than you
死丫头，你找死呀你
Dead wench, you seek dead ah you
你打我
You beat me
你们干什么？不要打了…
What are you dry?Not be beating …
不要打了，不要再打
Not be beating, don't beat again
不要打了…
Not be beating …
这么大的年纪还打架，不像话
The so big age still fights, too ridiculous
不要打了…
Not be beating …
妈妈，不要打了
Mother don't beat
不能打
Can not beat
不要打了…
Not be beating …
你们干什么？
What are you dry?
给我打，打…
Beat for me, beat …
不要打，白蒂
Don't dozen, white Di
妈，不要打
Mama don't beat
这是女子旅馆
This is the woman hotel
谁也不许在这儿摔架
Who also forbid to fall off here
好了…算了…
Like …calculate …
我求求你们了
I begged you
大家住在一起，还闹什么呢？
Everyone lives together and also make what?
她抢走了我的Darling
She rent away my Darling
老板看上我，又有什么办法？
What way does the boss have a liking for me, and then have?
不要脸
Shameless
谁不要脸？
Who shameless?
不要打了…
Not be beating …
算了，算了
Calculated, had already calculated
不要打了…
Not be beating …
来，坐下，坐下
Come, sit down, sit down
我来给大家介绍一下
I come to everyone and introduce once
这是新房客尤淑文小姐
This is bride chamber guest Ms. You Shu Wen
这是三号房的莉莲小姐
This is the Li lotus of the No.3 building young lady
Hello
露露小姐是在夜总会唱歌的
The dew exposes a young lady to sing a song in the night club
这是她的女儿珍妮
This is her daughter Jenny
还有这位是…
Still have this is …
我叫白蒂，我住五号房
I call white Di, I live No.5 building
我跟露露同一家夜总会
I expose the same night club with dew
站在我后头打马拉加斯
Stand to in back beat Ma La to add Si at me
快轮到我来主唱
Quick it's my turn to come to lord to sing
由你来打马拉加斯
BE beaten Ma La by you to add Si
到那个时候我宁愿死
Till that time I rather die
我可告诉你
I can tell you
白蒂看见人家的东西就想抢
The white Di sees the somebody else's thing wanting to rob
你要小心一点
You want caution a point
妈妈
Mother
她们都没受过什么教育
What do they have never been subjected to to educate
你不要见怪
You don't want to be offended
我是做女秘书的
I am to do a female secretary
我们的总经理都是晚上办公
All of our general managers transact in the evening
所以我白天睡觉，晚上才去上班的
So I go to bed in the daytime and just go to work in the evening
秘什么书呀？她是交际花
Mi what book ah?She is a social intercourse flower
我的朋友都是些大老板
My friends are all some big bosses
什么事呀？
What matter ah?
人家正睡得好好的
The somebody else is thoroughly sleeping
又让你们给吵醒了
Again make you give noisy awake
男人就喜欢毛手毛脚的
The man likes to flurry in movement
讨厌死了
Dislike to die
我来跟你们介绍
I come to introduce with you
这位歌拉是在旅行社做事的
This song pulls to work in the travel agency
这是教日语的南施小姐
This is south Ms. Shi who teaches Japanese
这是新搬来的尤淑文小姐
This is lately- moved Ms. You Shu Wen
我也是开夜班的，所以白天睡觉
I am also the class that opens a night of, so go to bed in the daytime
我是私家教师
I am a private teacher
告诉你，男人最贱了
Tell you, the man is the meanest
稍微给他们点好处
A little bit order an advantage for them
就马上给你小费
Give you the tips right away
还有谁没介绍过？
Still have who to haven't introduced?
哦，六号
, The sixth
Winnie呀
Winnie
这位是新来的…
This is newly arrived …
我叫Winnie
I call Winnie
我是研究古典舞蹈的
I am to study classic choreographic of
好，找个冤大头去
Like, seek a fool to go to
罗娜，你也来听听
Luo Nuo, you also listen to
刚才露露跟白蒂打架
Just dew the dew fight with white Di
归根结底都是因为男人
Return a knot bottoms all because of man
不负责任，自私自利
Irresponsible, selfish
我最恨男人
I hate a man most
所以我这儿禁止男人进来
So I forbid man to come in here
要是谁把男朋友带进来了
If who bring in boyfriend to come
就马上给我搬出去，知道了吗？
Move away for me right away, knew?
知道了
Know
她恨男人？她要不是跟男人好过
Does she hate a man?She if not that leading so much with man
怎么会养出个Tommy来
How can keep a Tommy to come
有了男人，这个世界才多彩多姿
There is man, this world is just colorful
对不对？
Right?
陈太太以前一定是给
Mrs. Chen before must be give
Tommy的爸爸欺负过
Tommy father once humiliates
所以才恨男人的
So just hate a man
我也这么想
I also think so
要不怎么这么恨男人呢？
Want to be not how hate so a man?
是不是？
BE be not?
你在什么地方做事？
Does your where work?
我从台北来找我妹妹的
I seek my younger sister from Taipei
找你妹妹？
Seek your younger sister?
我妹妹三个月以前来了香港
My younger sister 3 come to Hong Kong month past
以后就一直没消息了
Hereafter have been having no news
她叫尤淑慧
She calls You Shu Hui
你们有没有听过这个名字呀？
Have you ever listenned to this named?
没有…
Have no …
有个叫郭南昌的
There is calling Guo Nan Chang
不知道你们认不认识？
Don't know that you recognize incognizance?
郭南昌？
Guo Nan Chang?
你认得吗？
You recognize?
没听过这个名字
Have never listenned to this name
是姓郭的带她来的吗？
Is Xing Guo to take does she come?
我妹妹今年十八岁
This year of my younger sister is 18 years old
瘦瘦的，有一点像我
Thin thin of, be like me at 1:00
如果你们遇见了她，请通知我
If you met her, please notify me
我看一定是那个姓郭的拐骗了她
I see to be that abducting of surname Guo
不知道，也许是吧
Don't know, probably BE
真没出息
Really have no future
应该是女人骗男人才对
Should be a woman to cheat a man the rightness is just
你长得这么漂亮，身材又好
You grow so beautiful, shape again good
要是肯出来交际，一定行
If be willing to come out social intercourse, definitely go
肯定会迷倒很多男人
Affirming will be fond of to pour a lot of men
是啊，你肯不肯脱呀？
Yes, are you willing to take off?
脱？
Take off?
就是脱了衣服跳舞
Be took off clothes to dance
可不把男人喜欢看的地方
The place that can not like man to visit
都把它藏起来了
All hide it
什么古典舞蹈，简直胡说八道
What classic dance, absolutely talk nonsense
她是跳脱衣舞的
She is to do strip tease
你妈咪晚上出不出去呀？
Doesn't the your mummy's evening go out?
她要打牌
She wants to play cards
那么你又可以出来
So you can come out again
今天晚上我想替你接风，请你吃饭
I want to give a welcome party for you tonight and invite you to have a meal
如不反对，请敲地板三下，德生
If has no objection to, please knock floor three times, virtuous living
晚上八时在我房里等你，德生
Wait you in my building at 8:00 p.m., virtuous living
是六楼那个青年作曲家
Is the sixth floors that youth composer
太好了
Too good
憔悴憔悴
Distressed
是谁令你那么憔悴
BE who make you so distressed
是那将逝的腊梅
Being that will die of La plum
还是那未开的玫瑰
Or that rose that didn't open
是谁是谁
BE who is who
使是你心里受到伤害
Make is your in the mind to suffer from injury
好久不见
Long time no see
就算你流尽眼泪
Calculate you flow to the utmost tears
欢迎，欢迎，请里面坐
Welcome, welcome, please in sit
陈先生呢？
What about Mr. Chen?
在那边
Over there
老兄，我真羡慕你
You, I really envy you
有这么好的艳福
Have so good love affairs
可惜玫瑰多刺
The regrettable rose much stabs
我已经遍体鳞伤了
I already whole body covered with wounds
我倒愿意让这美丽的刺扎一下
I pour the sting that would like to make this beautiful firm once
陈先生真会说话
Mr. Chen really talks
请坐一会儿
The please sit down is in a short while
这个人真风趣
This person is true wit
早认识他就好了
Early know him good
这位是出名的花花公子
This is the famous playboy
你们千万要小心，别上当
You must be careful, don't fall into trap
着迷着迷
Infatuate
哪里才有真情存在
Where just existence genuine feeling
如果你执迷不悟
If you are perverse
只添多几分憔悴
Adds much and are distressed for several cents
露露已经老了
Dew the dew have been old
换换别人来唱吧
Change other people to come to sing
连老相好都不想要了？
Connect old fond of each other all don't want?
玩久了也会厌
Playing is long will also be disgusted with
待会儿叫她来见我
After a while call she to see me
佐治
The Zuo cures
吴老兄，吴老兄，你好，你好
You Wu, you Wu, how are you, you good
丁莲小姐，你今天晚上真漂亮
D lotus young lady, you are true tonight beautiful
谢谢你
Thank you
每天晚上也换一个女伴
Also change a female companion every evening
吴老兄，你的艳福可真不浅
You Wu, you of the love affairs is really not shallow
我们说正经的好吧？
We say serious all right?
今天晚上还有没有兴趣？
Still have interest tonight?
玩牌是吧？
Playing the card BE?
好，我要把输给你的全都赢回来
Like, I want lose to you of all win back
每一次都是我输，那怎么行？
Every time is that I lose, how does that go?
老板，今天晚上
Boss, tonight
你也带一位漂亮的小姐来吧
You also take a beautiful young lady to come
那当然了
That was certainly
我陈某人一辈子就是为了女人
My someone Chen during a lifetime be for the sake of woman
好啦！早点来呀
Good!Come earlier
正在做功课呀？多用功呀
BE doing homework?Much hard working
你要出去呀？
Do you want to go out?
拜拜…
Worship …
我来了
I came
你？
You?
我叫Winnie，你不认识我吗？
I call Winnie, your incognizance I?
我常在电梯上碰到你
I often run into you on the elevator
我没想到你会请我吃饭
I have never thought you will invite me to have a meal
可以走了吗？
Is it all right to walk?
不…请你放尊重一点
Not …invite you to put to respect 1:00
年轻人应该及时行乐才对
The young man should make merry while one can a rightness just
别太正经吧
Don't be too serious
我…
I …
来嘛，来…
Come, come …
奇怪，怎么还不来？
Strange, how still don't come?
我照他摔给你看
I shine on he falls off to let you see
你会吗？
Your meeting?
当然会，用力一摔
Make an effort a to fall off certainly
好极了…
Just splendid …
然后我再把他拉起来
Then I then pull him
你没事吧？
You are all right?
怎么啦？
How?
你要出去呀？
Do you want to go out?
楼下的王先生约我去吃饭
Mr. Wang of down stairs invites I have a meal
王先生？
Mr. Wang?
真的吗？
Really?
王先生是一个很好的作曲家
Mr. Wang is a good composer
你要好好把握机会
You are good friends with to seize the opportunity so much
Tommy，你怎么可以进来的呢？
Tommy, how could you come in?
妈咪不在家，大家都同意的
The mummy isn't at home, everyone agrees
这个世界上要是没有男人
This is in the world were it not for man
那还像话吗？
That returns reasonable?
你也该休息休息了
You should also take a rest to take a rest
别老是盯着人家
Don't always stare at a somebody else
你说他们在约会的时候做些什么？
While saying that they are in the appointment what do you do?
那一定是Kiss嘛
That must be Kiss
啊，Kiss？
, Kiss?
救命呀，不要…
Help ah, don't…
尤小姐，她…我…
Ms. You, she …I …
你约了我，又约她？
Did you invite me and invite her again?
尤小姐，你不要误会
Ms. You, you don't want to misunderstand
你看看
You see
这不是你给我的信吗？
Isn't this the letter that you give me?
这样被人家作弄
BE so teased by the somebody else
我还是第一次呢
I still for the first time
真倒霉
True unlucky
什么话？
What rubbish?
叫我打马拉加斯？
Call me to beat Ma La to add Si?
只要客人不爱听你的歌
Want ～only the guest doesn't love to listen to you of song
照理可以请你滚蛋的
Shining on the reason can invite what you fuck off
现在看在我们的交情上
On the friendship that sees at us now
让你来替白蒂
Let you to substitute white Di
你还可以拿到一半的薪水
You can also get hold of half of salaries
是不是白蒂来顶替我的位置？
Isn't a white Di to take over my position?
我就是这个意思
I am this meaning
亏你还说得出口
Kui you still say export
当初我走红的时候
At the beginning while aming popular I
每天缠着我说一大堆甜言蜜语的
Worry every day I say a lot of sweet talk
是谁？
BE who?
那是过去的事了，小姐
That was the past matter, young lady
我不干
I ain't dry
让我打马拉加斯，我宁愿死了
Let me beat Ma La to add Si, I rather died
白蒂，从现在起
White Di, from now on
你就是我的正式歌星了
You were my formal singer
佐治，你真好
The Zuo cures, you are really good
今天晚上没问题吧？
All right tonight?
没问题
All right
我已经跟丁莲约好了
I already the heel D lotus invite
上一次我跟她合作
I cooperated with her last time
你不是赢钱了吗？
You not is win money?
这一次你说说看怎么报答我？
Did you say to see how to recompense me this time?
我早就准备好了，小姐
I early get ready, young lady
老板
Boss
进来都不敲门，太没有礼貌了
Come in all don't knock on door, too ill-mannered
咱们俩的关系还用得着敲门吗？
The relation of we two still uses wear to knock on door?
看看人家既年轻又漂亮
See a somebody else since young and beautiful
怪不得会把露露给赶走了呢
No wonder that will expose the dew to kick out
佐治，我告诉你
The Zuo cures, I tell you
我不会像露露那样的
I can't be like dew dew so of
你放心好了
You trust
原来你跟那个脱衣舞娘也有一手
Originally you also have a skill with that striper
我跟她只是玩玩
My heel she just plays
我对你才是真爱
I are a true love to you
小心
Carefully
你要是像露露那样甩掉我的话
If you are like dew to expose so fling off my words
我可不客气
I can be Don't mention it
我先把你砍上十几刀
I chop down you first up ten several knifes
女人说这种话的时候
While saying this kind of words woman
真是可爱极了
Is really lovely pole
这次可别飞错了
Doing not fly this time is wrong
（纸飞机偏了航线，很对不起）
(The paper airplane was partial to flight path, very sorry)
（我弹首曲子，以示歉意，德生）
(I play a song to show apology, virtuous living)
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
虽然大小快慢不一般
Although all of the rate of speed aren't general
只要方向看得准
Want ～only a direction to see quasi-ly
自然送你到彼岸
Send you to the other shore naturally
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
永远上下起伏波涛泛
Up and down rise and fall big waves to be suffused with forever
只要船儿把得稳
Want ～only ship son chase steady
我也亲你一下吧
I also kiss you once
怎么亲法？我不懂的
Close method how?I don't understand
我也不懂
I don't understand as well
纵然遇到狂风和巨浪
Even if meet strong breeze and billow
不用惊怕不用慌
Need not fear need not panic
挺起胸膛往前闯
Rush before sticking out the chest to
渡过东部大海洋
Pass through eastern big ocean
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
你我西东漂流在四方
You my west east drift at everywhere
但求随遇而能安
But beg with meet but ability Anne
浪花朵朵…
Wave blossom …
他怎么会弹这首歌？
Does he how can play this song?
王先生，你怎么会弹这首歌？
Mr. Wang, do you how can play this song?
你又是怎么会唱的呢？
You again is how can sing?
这首歌是我父亲作的曲
This song is the song that my father makes
我跟妹妹在台北的时候经常唱的
My heel younger sister the time in Taipei usually sing
你是在哪儿学的？
Are you where to learn?
奇怪，我们学音乐的
Strange, we learn musical
要是有好的旋律总是把它记下来
If there is a good melody always recording it down
我帮你想想在哪儿听到的
Where do I want to hear for you
你要仔细的想想
You want to cautiously want
这是找我妹妹的唯一线索
This is the only clues that seeks my younger sister
奇怪，又不是广播
Strange, again not is broadcasting
又不是在电视
Isn't on TV again
我是在哪儿听到的？
Am I where to hear?
怎么想不起来呢？
How to can not recall?
妈，妈，怎么啦？
Mama, mama, how?
酒…
Wine …
阿姨
Aunt
酒，快拿酒来
Wine take wine quickly
阿姨，你喝醉了
Aunt, you get drunk
坐
Sit
白蒂，哪儿比得上我？
White Di, where peter last I?
是啊
Yes
我的歌不是很受欢迎吗？
Isn't my song greatly popular?
怎么醉成这个样子
How to inebriate into this appearance
我也不知道
I don't know as well
快扶她进房去吧
Hand quickly she enters building to go
虽然大小快慢不一般
Although all of the rate of speed aren't general
这首歌是…
This song is …
妈常唱这首歌的
Mama often sings this song
只要方向看得准
Want ～only a direction to see quasi-ly
自然送你到彼岸
Send you to the other shore naturally
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
这是台湾来的歌
This is the song that Taiwan comes
你妈妈怎么会唱呢？
Does your mother how can sing?
大概是在夜总会听到的
Probably hear in the night club
我还年青，绝不会输给她
I return young, in no case will lose to her
只要方向看得准
Want ～only a direction to see quasi-ly
自然送你到彼岸
Send you to the other shore naturally
妈妈…
Mother …
听着，愈上是愈好牌
Listenning to up is a good card more more
头顶是同花大顺
The top of head is greatly and fluently to together spend
摸头发是同花顺
Touching the hair is to together spend to follow
眉毛是四张
The eyebrow is 4
鼻子是FullHouse
The nose is FullHouse
擦口红…
Wipe lipstick …
擦口红就是顺子
Wiping the lipstick is an agreeable son
摸耳环是三张
Touching the earring is 3
手表或者手镯是两对
Watch or bracelet are 2 rightnesses
戒子是一对
The ring is 1 rightness
我的红利是十分之一
My bonus is pretty much of a
不要忘记了
Don't forget
四百
多少？四百
How much?400
好，跟了
Like, heel
又是我
Is me again
多少？
How much?
还是四百
Or 400
这回可好了
This time good
多下点吧
Much next point
五百
跟
Heel
两条顺
Twos are agreeable
你是一对，我是两条顺
You are 1 rightness, I am that twos are agreeable
再加八百
Add again 800
Boy，拔兰地
Boy pulls out orchid ground
好，我跟
Like, my heel
再加六百
Add again 600
下点吧
Next point
六百之后，梭哈，请
600 after, the shuttle admires and please
好
Good
我输了
I lost
Boy，再拿筹码来
Boy takes a counter again
从现在开始，我们筹码加倍
From now on, our counter double
好
Good
没关系，一副牌就回来
It doesn't matter, a card comes back
你真好，真舒服
You are really good, true comfortable
干嘛动手动脚的
Why make physical advances
怎么老打人？讨厌
How old hit persons?Dislike
收了工以后，你陪陪我好不好？
After stopping work for the day, you go along with me not very good?
我才不要你这个无赖呢
I just don't your this loafer
有什么了不起
Have what fantastic
上一次洗澡的钱你还没有给我
Money that took a shower last time you haven't given me
老提钱干什么，我们是老相好
Old lift money of stem what, we are old to fond of each other
谁是你的老相好，快点进来
Who is you of old fond of each other, quickly come in
死鬼
You damn fool
怎么老打人呀？罗娜
How old hit persons?Luo Nuo
真舒服
True comfortable
这样大力干什么？
Devote major efforts like this dry what?
罗娜
Luo Nuo
那么你跟我介绍一个好不好？
So you introduce one with me not very good?
你要我介绍一个给你呀
You want me to introduce 1 to you
可是你不是小白脸
But you aren't a small white face
你又不肯多花钱
You aren't willing to spend money more again
还没人要你呢
Return nobody to want you
我难看
I am difficult to see
当然啰，扭扭捏捏的那像个男人
Certainly, bashful of that is like a men
我看你还是老实点吧
I see you still the honesty order
没人会喜欢你这种男人的
The nobody will like your this kind of man
什么话？说得那么难听
What rubbish?Say so unpleasant to hearly
你要是想找女人的话
If you want to seek chemisette words
除非你肯多花钱
Unless you are willing to spend money more
该花的地方我一定花
The place shoulded spend I definitely spend
但是你要跟我找一个漂亮的
But you want to seek one with me to be beautiful
那我的介绍费呢？
What about that my introduction fee?
我一定会给你的
I will definitely give you
好的，先把旧帐还清
Okay, repay fully old debt first
连以前欠我的一共是一百块钱
It is 100 dollars to connect before and owe my totally
你先把钱还给我
You return money to me first
我就答应介绍一个给你
I promise to introduce 1 to you
对不起，我忘了带钱
Execuse me, I forgot to carry money
下次一块给你
A cake of gives you next time
你少来这一套
You are little to come to this set of
我才不信你的鬼话呢
I just don't believe you of outright lies
一会儿说是给朋友借去了
In a short while say is borrow for friend to go to
一会儿说是打麻将输了
In a short while say is play mahjong to lose
其实全是胡说八道骗人的
In fact whole rubbish bogus
烫死我了，快放我出来
Very hot die I, put quickly I come out
你不守信用，就别怪我辣手了
You don't keep promise, don't blame me a hot hand
我实在是没有钱呀罗娜
I really have no money ah Luo Nuo
嫌不够热的话
Dislike the words of not enough heat
我再给你开大一点
I then open for you a little bit bigger
不要再开大
Don't open again greatly
你给不给钱？
Do you give money?
实在是没有钱呀罗娜
Really have no money ah Luo Nuo
我没有钱
I have no rich
我自己去拿
I take by myself
罗娜，不要翻我的衣服…
Luo Nuo don't turn over my clothes …
我的皮包
My wallet
你不是说你没带钱吗？
You not is say that you didn't carry money?
那不是我的钱，那是人家的
That isn't my money, that is the somebody else
管它谁的，我先拿着
Take care of its whose, I take first
你要是不给我钱的话
If you the words that don't give me money
我就不放你出来
I don't put you come out
我给，给呀，我给
I give and give ah, I give
这可是你心甘情愿的
This is that you is willingly of
烫死了
Very hot die
活该
What a suck
陈太太，早
Mrs. Chen, early
早
Early
露露呢？
Does the dew expose?
她们过夜生活的人
They lead the person of night life
现在正在睡觉呢
BE going to bed now
吃早点吧
Eat breakfast
我先去看看她去
I go first to see she goes to
早
Early
谁呀？
Who ah?
是我，淑文呀
Is me, Shu text
好点了吗？
Good point?
我的头还有点疼
My head has some painful
我听珍妮说
I listen to Jenny saying
昨天晚上幸亏你照应我
The last night thanks to you look after me
谢谢你
Thank you
哪里，珍妮呢？
Where, and Jenny?
上学去了
Go to at school
她明年就要毕业了
She is about to graduate next year
我宁愿自己吃点苦
I prefer to I eat to order a bitterness
也要让她念完中学
Also want to make her finish reading aloud a high school
靠你一个人真不容易呀
Depend you a personal true not easy
你先生呢？
What about your husband?
在十年前已经死了
Have already died by decade
他一死，我可就苦了
He is one dead, I can bitterness
我觉得女人是要依靠男人的
I feel that the woman wants to depend on a man
可是我所遇到的男人
But the man met by me
却没有一个好人
But have no a good man
我觉得我一生下来
I feel that I come down from cradle to the grave
就注定是命苦的
Destine is hard luck
我想请问你一下
I would like to ask you
昨天晚上你喝醉酒的时候
While getting drunk wine last night you
唱的那首歌
The song of singing
是在哪儿学来的？
Is where to learn to come?
什么歌？
What song?
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
虽然大小快慢不一般
Although all of the rate of speed aren't general
那是经理给我的歌谱
That is the music score that the manager gives me
他说这首歌在台湾很流行
He says that this song is very popular in Taiwan
你们经理是不是叫郭南昌呀？
Is your manager to call Guo Nan Chang?
不，叫谭逊
Call Tan Xun not
怎么啦？
How?
本来我跟我妹妹在台北一起唱歌的
Originally I sang a song together in Taipei with my younger sister
听说那个姓郭的中年人
Hear that surname Guo's middle age
长得很smart
Grow very smart
他带我妹妹到香港来登台
He brings my younger sister to Hong Kong to go on stage
不知道会不会是你们经理？
Don't know that the meeting can't be your manager?
不会的
Can't of
我们经理的样子
Our manager's appearance
长得就像女人一样，扭扭捏捏的
Grow to be like a woman, bashful
人也很小气
The person is also very stingy
那他怎么会有那张歌谱呢？
That does he how can have that music score?
如果有客人点唱
If the guest orders to sing
我们就写信到台湾去要来
We write a letter to go to Taiwan and come
对不起，真麻烦你了
Execuse me, troublesome you
你多歇一会儿吧
You many Xies is in a short while
没关系
Don't relate to
坐呀
Sit
早  早
Early and early
早餐一块二
Breakfast a cake of two
中饭，晚饭两块
Lunch, supper 2 piece
听说你在找你的妹妹
Hear you at seek you of younger sister
她叫什么名字？
What name does she call?
她叫尤淑慧
She calls You Shu Hui
尤淑慧？
You Shu Hui?
她几岁呀？
Is she how old?
今年十八岁了
This year is 18 years old
你们认不认识她？
You recognize incognizant she?
我们店里有个新同事也是姓尤的
There is a new colleague in our store is also Xing You
她的年纪好像跟你说的差不多
Her age seems to be with what you said about
是真的吗？
Is true?
我们那儿也有一个叫淑慧
We also have there a call Shu Hui
不过是姓黄
However is Xing Huang
哦，姓黄？
, Xing Huang?
也许改了姓也说不定
Probably changed a surname also perhaps
你应该去看看嘛
You should see
对，去看看
To, see
我带你去看看
I take you see
进来吧
Come in
尤小姐，你来
Ms. You, you come
过来
Come over
是你呀
Is you
你叫什么名字？
What name do you call?
美玲
Beautiful Ling
什么事呀？
What matter ah?
我们本来以为你是她妹妹
We originally thought that you were her younger sister
对了，我现在想起来了
To, I thought of now
她从来没说过她妹妹有雀斑
She has never said that her younger sister has freckle
来，她就在那儿
Come, she where
淑慧，你过来看看是不是你姐姐
Shu Hui, you come over and see isn't your elder sister
姐姐？
Elder sister?
妹妹我倒有十个
Younger sister pours to have 10
姐姐我是一个也没有
Elder sister am also 1 to have no
十个妹妹？
Ten younger sisters?
奇怪什么
What is oddness
我妈平均三年生两个
Living 2 for my mama average three years
有一年还来个双胞胎呢
Have a year to return to twins
你爸爸妈妈真是努力生产
The your father mother is really a diligent production
是不是她？
Is her?
不是的
Not yes
尤小姐
Ms. You
王先生
Mr. Wang
你怎么也来了？
How did you also come?
她们带我到这儿来找我妹妹
They take I arrive here to seek my younger sister
可是一个都不是的
But none of 1 is yes
有什么关系呢？
What relate to?
慢慢找总会找到的
Slowly seek what head quarters find out
你只不过才来了一天
You only just come to a day
可是一点线索也没有
But some clues also have no
真叫人担心
Let everybody to worry
不要担心，线索总有的
Don't worry, the clues always has
就是那支歌
Is that song
昨天我想了一个晚上
Yesterday I thought for a night
人生人生就像一条船…
The life life is like a ship …
不晓得在什么地方听过
Don't know a where to once listen to
现在连这点线索也没有用了
Now connect this clues don't also use
那个露露也会唱这支歌
That dew dew will also sing this song
听说是在哪个夜总会里学来的
Hear is which night club in learn to come
夜总会？夜总会
Night club?Night club
对了
To
有一家夜总会介绍来录音的小姐
There is a night club introducing to a taped young lady
也会唱的
Will also sing
真的吗？
Really?
我们公司里一定有她的录音带，走
There is definitely her tape in our company and walk
那一颗心…
That heart …
不对
Not rightness
这个也不对
This also not rightness
主唱人尤小姐
The lord sings person, Ms. You,
再听听看
Listen to again
…在我心头…
…In my at heart …
对了，对了
To, to
这就是我妹妹的声音
This is my younger sister's voice
不会错的，再倒回去听听
Inerrable, pour again to return to listen to
好，好
Like, good
由金龙夜总会经理介绍来的
The night club dragon manager of gold introduces to come
主唱人尤小姐
The lord sings person, Ms. You,
金龙？
Gold dragon?
就是露露在唱的那间夜总会
Is a dew dew at sing of the night club
这样好了，我们去问问看
Like this like, we ask to see
谁找我？
Who seek me?
是这两位
Is these 2
二位找我有什么事吗？
2 seek what matter do I have?
请问你是谭经理吗？
Are you manager Tan?
是的，我就是谭逊
Yes, I am Tan Xun
样子好像女人一样
The appearance seems to be woman
扭扭捏捏的小气鬼
Bashful cheap stake
Lulu说的原来就是你呀
Lulu says of is you
说话客气一点嘛
Talk a little bit more polite
我是美都唱片公司的
I am all the United States record company of
谭经理，三个月之前
Manager Tan, three months ago
你介绍一位尤小姐去录音
You introduce a Ms. You to record sound
尤小姐，我…
Ms. You, I …
就是我妹妹
Is my younger sister
从台湾来的，瘦瘦的个子
From Taiwan come of, thin thin of statures
今年十八岁
This year is 18 years old
她呀，我不认识
She ah, I am incognizant
但是根据录音带是由你介绍的
But is introduced by you according to the tape
也许是我的老朋友
Probably is my old friend
冒认我的名字也不一定
The name that assumes false identity me is also uncertain
你老朋友有没有叫郭南昌的？
Does your old friend have to call Guo Nan Chang?
郭南昌？
Guo Nan Chang?
我根本没有这个朋友
I basically have no this friend
对了，也许人家冒用我的名字
To, probably the somebody else falsely use my name
因为我在娱乐界是很有地位的
Because I at amuse boundary is have much of a position
你要是想做电影明星
If you want to do movie star
或者是歌星的话
Or is the singer's words
最好由我来介绍
Had better be introduced by me
我帮你一定OK
I help you the certain OK
在圈子里做事一定要有后台才行
At the turn work in son must have backstage to just go
尤小姐是不是…
Ms. You is be not …
如果有消息的话请你通知我
If there are the words of news ask you to notify me
我叫尤淑文
I call You Shu Wen
我住在光华大厦八楼
I live in the glory mansion eighth floors
当然，当然
Certainly, certainly
美雅公寓
Beautiful graceful apartment
是的，慢走，慢走
Walk yes and slowly, slowly walk
有空来玩，来呀，来玩呀
Free to have fun, come, have fun
再见，再见
See again, again see
什么？美雅公寓
What?Beautiful graceful apartment
那不是罗娜住的地方
That isn't the place that Luo Nuo lives
喂，我是罗娜，原来是你呀？
Feed, am I Luo Nuo, is you?
怎么啦？我就不能打电话给你呀
How?I can not make a phone call to you
罗娜，我请你帮个忙好不好？
Luo Nuo, I invite you to do some help not very good?
你那儿不是有个房客姓尤的吗？
You are there not is have a tenant Xing You of?
你替我想想办法，好不好？
You arrange somehow for me, not very good?
你能出多少介绍费？
Your ability how much introduce a fee?
不管成不成功都要给的
No matter don't successfully become to all want to of
只要你给钱的话
Want ～only you to the words of money
我就答应替你想办法
I promise to think a way for you
好的
Good of
尤小姐，出去了？
Ms. You went out?
一早就出去了
Go out early in the morning
你天天在练习？
Are you practicing every day?
是呀，我快考黑带了
BE ah, I test quickly black take
我跟你试试怎么样？
I try with you how?
你不怕？摔疼了我不管
Aren't you afraid?Falling off is painful I ignore
我不怕
I ain't afraid
抓这儿，脚放这儿
Grasp here, the feet put here
我的柔道怎么样？
How is my judo?
要是遇见色狼足够应付的
If meet sex maniac to enough cope with
你跟我比呀，差得远啦
You compare with me ah, differ a great deal
怎么啦？
How?
她太不应该了
She too should not
趁我不注意，把我摔倒
Take advantage o my inattention, fall down me
你快回房去
You return to building quickly
你妈妈就要回来了
Your mother is about to come back
露露，听说你辞职了
Dew dew hears that you resigned
给一个不要脸的贱货
Give a shameless mean person
害得我连饭碗也丢了
Harm I even the bowl also threw
女人一上了年纪
Woman an ascend age
爱情青春美貌饭碗都会丢的
The love youth beautiful looks bowls will throw
会增加的只有脸上的皱纹
Will increase of only have the crease on the face
这是上帝的安排
This is the god's arrangement
你看，这是佐治送给我的
You see, this is the Zuo to cure to send to my
你不要得意忘形
You don't want to be dizzy with success
总有一天，你呀也会跟我一样
One day there will, you ah will also similar to me
所以我要趁着年轻的时候多赚点钱
So while wanting to take to be young, I earn some money more
白蒂
White Di
昨天晚上的红利呢？
What about last night's bonus?
赢了四千块是不是？
Won 4,000 pieces is be not?
我要十分之一
I want pretty much of a
佐治只肯给我两百
The Zuo cures to give me 200
我们一人一半，这个是你的
The half of our one person, this is you
一百块？佐治这个人真小气
100 piece?The Zuo cures this person true stingy
今天晚上是我第一次正式的登台
The tonight is that I formally go on stage for the first time
我一定要好好的唱
I must thoroughly sing
淑文，找到你妹妹没有？
Shu text has already found out your younger sister?
还没有找到
Haven't found out
我也到处打听你妹妹的下落
I also find out your younger sister's whereabouts everywhere
有个客人告诉我，他好像见过她
A guest tells me, he seemed to once see her
是真的？
Is true?
当然真的，他会来看我的
Certainly true of, he will see my
这是我的地址，你来好了
This is my address, you come
土耳其浴室
Bathroom in Turkey
请妳再唱那首歌好吗？
Would you mind singing that song again?
她不在家？
She not is at home?
什么事？
What matter?
请问罗娜小姐在吗？
Excuse me, Luo Nuo young lady at?
哦，你就是尤小姐
, You are Ms. You
是的
Yes
在那边，五号房
Over there, No.5 building
谢谢你
Thank you
还不来呢？
Still don't come?
来了
Come
尤小姐
Ms. You
是你？
Is you?
罗娜呢？
What about Luo Nuo?
罗娜跟客人出去了
Luo Nuo went out with guest
尤小姐，你真是把我想死了
Ms. You, you were to want me to die
现在我们两个可以好好的玩一玩
Now we 2 can thoroughly have fun
陈太太，尤小姐回来了没有？
Mrs. Chen, has Ms. You already come back?
还没回来呢，你有什么事吗？
Haven't come back, what matter do you have?
没事没事
Have no a matter have no matter
王先生
Mr. Wang
罗娜叫她到浴室去
Luo Nuo calls her to go to bathroom
说是介绍什么人
Say that is introduction what person
罗娜叫她去呀？
Does Luo Nuo call her to go to?
我也觉得奇怪
I also feel strange
到底什么事？
Exactly what matter?
我告诉你
I tell you
她是在土耳其浴室做事的
She works in bathroom in Turkey
土耳其浴室
Bathroom in Turkey
不要…
Don't…
让我亲一下
Make me close once
你要干什么？
Do you want to do what?
那你到这儿来干什么？
That do you arrive to come to do what here?
那你不是要钱吗？
That don't you want money?
你看，我有的是钱
You see, I have plenty of money
你不要污辱我
You don't want to insult me
钱都不要，真是
None of money wants, be really
我来的目的是因为罗娜告诉我
The purpose that I come because Luo Nuo tells me
你知道我妹妹的下落
You know my younger sister's whereabouts
并不是为了钱
Isn't for money
你妹妹的下落只有我知道
Your younger sister's whereabouts only I know
真的吗？
Really?
你让我亲一下，我就告诉你
You make me close once, I tell you
你妹妹是夜总会老板
Your younger sister is a night club boss
让我带到录音公司
Let me take a recording company
啊，你老板？
, Your boss?
到录音公司试了音
Arrived recording company to try a sound
以后的事我慢慢告诉你
Later matter I slowly tell you
来，让我亲一下吧
Come, make me close once
我问你，尤小姐在什么地方？
I ask you, Ms. You's where?
五号房
No.5 building
你干什么？
What are you dry?
你要干什么？
Do you want to do what?
德生
Virtuous living
千万不要误会我
Never misunderstand me
我对她是一番好意
I is some kind of good intentionses to her
可是她不了解我
But she doesn't understand me
我发誓，我也没有对她怎么样
I swear that I also have no to how is she
再见
See again
回来，想走呀你
Come back, want to walk ah you
你要怎么样？
How are you?
今天开心死了
Happy die today
我的演出非常的成功
My performance very of successful
客人53个
53 guests
有些客人还亲到后台来看我
Some guests still arrive backstage to see me in person
口渴死了
Thirsty die
你喝杯茶
You drink cup tea
谢谢
Thank
佐治他非常欣赏我的歌
The Zuo cures the song that he appreciates me very much
他说要是早知道我唱得那么好
He says if early know that I sing so goodly
早就让我主唱了
Early make me main to sing
真是谢谢你
Really thank you
拜拜
Worship
他叫我从明天起
He calls me since tomorrow
要我一边唱歌一边跳舞
Want me simultaneously sing a song part dancing
我说我不会跳
I say that I can't jump
他说不要紧
He says unimportant
我年轻，只要这么扭扭腰
I am young and want ～only to twist so a waist
客人就会高兴的
The guest will be happy
什么事那么高兴呀？
What matter so happy?
等一等
Wait a minute
露露
The dew exposes
青酸钾
Green sour potassium
半夜三更的，你们吵什么？
Late at night of, what are you noisy?
对不起
Sorry
我不小心把一个茶壶打翻了
I carelessly tipped over a teapot
下次小心点，快点收拾好了
Carefully order next time, quickly put away
是
BE
露露，你…
The dew exposes, you …
妈，怎么啦？
Mama, how?
没什么，我跟你妈妈在谈点事情
Nothing important, my heel your mother at talk some affair
没什么，你回去睡觉吧
Nothing important, you return to a sleeping
快去睡呀  去呀
Sleep quickly ah go to
快去  去
Go to quickly
不错
Quite good
我要杀死白蒂，我恨她
I want to kill white Di, I hate her
她把我的饭碗，佐治都抢走了
She chases my bowl, the Zuo cured to all rend away
谁是佐治？
Who is it the Zuo that cure?
是我们的老板
Is our bosses
一个中年的花花公子
A playboy of middle age
中年的花花公子？
The playboy of middle age?
见到漂亮的女人就要追
Seeing the beautiful woman will make track for
玩厌了一个又换一个
Was disgusted with playing 1 and change 1
虽然我知道早晚会被他甩掉
Although I know will be flung off by him sooner or later
可是我为了要保存饭碗
But I am in order to keep bowl
才跟他接近
Just is close with him
没想到白蒂把他抢走了
The unexpectedly white Di rent away him
拐走我的妹妹会不会是佐治
The younger sister meeting that kidnaps me can't be a Zuo to cure
我想起来了
I thought of
那张歌谱是佐治给我的
That music score is a Zuo to cure to my
对了，我也听说过
To, I once heard as well
他从台湾带了一个歌星来
He took a singer to come from Taiwan
那么佐治可能就是郭南昌
So the Zuo cures to be Guo Nan Chang
从台湾来的歌星也许就是我妹妹
The singer who comes from Taiwan is probably my younger sister
她现在是不是还在夜总会演唱呀？
She now whether still just does the night club sing on stage?
不
Not
她知道佐治有很多的女朋友
She knows that the Zuo cures to have a lot of girl friends
一气之下就跑了
In a pet run
啊！
!
以后再也没有听到她的消息了
Hereafter the news that didn't hear her any further
是不是有办法查一查呢？
Whether there is a way checking?
你会不会唱歌？
Can't your meeting sing a song?
会呀，我在台北是唱歌的
Meeting ah, I am in Taipei is sing a song
那就对了
That to
你可以到金龙夜总会去唱
You can arrive a gold night club dragon sing
我走了以后，白蒂在唱
I after walking, white Di at sing
我相信你一定可以把她赶走
I believe that you can definitely kick out her
由你来主唱
You come to lord to sing
他们会不会请我？
Can't their meeting invite me?
你放心吧
You stop worrying
佐治一看见漂亮女人就着迷
The Zuo cures a to see the beautiful woman infatuating
你就利用这一点向他进攻
You make use of this to take the offensive toward him
可是我不会
But I can't
那很容易，只要化浓一点的妆
That is very easy and only turn a little bit thicker of makeup
灌他几句迷汤
Infuse him several fan soup
他就会上勾了
He will ascend to hang up
还有，贴一个假痣
Still have, stick a false birthmark
穿一件低胸的衣服
Wear a clothes of low chest
把胸部挺得高高的
Stand chest very high
他喜欢肉弹型的女人
He likes the woman of buxom beauty type
为了你的妹妹
For the sake of you of younger sister
你一定要去试一试
You must try and see
露露，你也来了？
Dew dew, did you also come?
让开，让开
Step aside, step aside
露露小姐，你好吗？
The dew exposes a young lady, are you good?
今天我是这儿的客人
I am the guest here today
好，今天晚上就让我来请客
Like, the tonight lets I to pay
请你介绍这位漂亮的小姐
Please introduce this beautiful young lady
给我认识
Give me the understanding
这是我的朋友尤小姐
This is my friend, Ms. You,
他是这儿的老板佐治陈
He is boss Zuo here to cure Chen
Hello
在我认识的太太小姐当中
Ms. wife, who know at me, is in the middle
你是长得最漂亮的一个
You are to grow the most beautiful a
谢谢你
Thank you
实在是太漂亮了
Really beautiful
也许是丁香，也许是蔷薇
Probably being a lilac is probably a rambling rose
看起来不是很美丽
Look isn't beauty very
可是亲手培植的花
But personally the flower of implantation
怎能够随意来抛弃
How did you can at will abandon
佐治，尤小姐也会唱歌
The Zuo cures, Ms. You will also sing a song
比白蒂要好得多了
It's a sight better to compare white Di to want
真的吗？
Really?
尤小姐
Ms. You
今天到我这儿来唱好不好？
Today arrive I here to sing not very good?
你说呀
You say
那要看看条件了
That wanted to see a condition
只要你答应，多少钱都可以
As long as you promise, how much all can
怎么样？
How?
我们现在就到外面找个地方
We is an outside to seek a place now
谈谈合同，好不好？
Discuss contract, not very good?
好呀，那你快去吧
Good ah, that you go quickly
今天不行
Don't go today
那么明天怎么样？
So tomorrow how?
哪间酒店好？
Which cabaret good?
我久慕的他曾不理
I long Mu of he once ignored
我不要到酒店去
I don't want a cabaret
那么到我家来吧，明天晚上
So arrive my house come, tomorrow evening
白天比较好
Better in the daytime
明天下午我到你别墅来
I will arrive your villa tomorrow afternoon
Okay
我在那儿等你，下午四点
I where wait you, 4:00 p.m.
好的
Good of
走吧
Leave
我不要听这种蹩脚的歌
I don't want to listen to this kind of inferior song
走
Walk
露露，怎么就要走了？
Dew how be the dew about to walk?
谁呀？真是
Who ah?Be really
别啰嗦
Don't be bothersome
死相，老不死的老色迷
Dead mutually, the old deathless old color is fond of
老板，你刚换了白蒂没有几天
Boss, you just changed white Di to have no several days
现在又不想要人家了
Now again don't want a somebody else
你这样做未免太过份一点了吧
You like this do to is too 1:00
这有什么过份的
This has what excessive of
我实实在在喜欢她
I am actually true at like her
可以说我有生以来
It's from birth to can say me
我头一次遇到一个
I first meet 1
我真正爱上她的人
I am real to fall in love with her person
多待一天，先吊吊他的胃口
Treat one more day, hang his appetite first
你明天还要化妆浓一点
You will still need to make up tomorrow a little bit thicker
我一个人不敢去呀
My a person doesn't dare to go
为了你的妹妹，要拿出勇气来
For the sake of you of younger sister, take out courage
这一次白蒂要丢饭碗了
The white Di wanted to throw bowl this time
活该
What a suck
王先生
Mr. Wang
淑文呢？
What about Shu text?
我想当然在房里
I think certainly in the building
我有事要找她
I occupy and seek her
我有要紧的事
I have an important matter
你要快点
You have to hurry
等一下陈太太回来，那可糟了
Wait for a second Mrs. Chen come back, that is in a mess
我知道
I know
谁呀？
Who ah?
是我，德生
Is me, virtuous living
你怎么可以进来的呢
Do you how to come in
男宾止步，我知道
The male guest halts, I know
现在不管这些
Now ignore these
我有天大的好消息告诉你
I have 1-day-old good news to tell you
到底怎么回事？
Exactly and what is the row?
这个礼拜天你就可以上电视了
You can ascend a television this Sunday
你在电视里唱那首歌
You on TV in sing that song
你妹妹一定会来找你的
Your younger sister will definitely seek you
真的吗？
Really?
我把一切的情形告诉我们台长
I the whole of the situation tell us set long
台长很愿意帮助我们
The set is long would like to help us very much
所以我特地跑来告诉你
So I specially run to tell you
你这是什么意思？
You is this what mean?
你怎么打扮成这个样子？
How do you disguise as this appearance?
拐走我妹妹的
Kidnap my younger sister
就是金龙夜总会的老板佐治陈
Is boss Zuo of gold night club dragon to cure Chen
露露介绍我跟他谈合同
Expose a dew to introduce me to talk contract with him
我要接近他
I want to approach him
我想跟他打听一下
I want with him and find out once
关于我妹妹的下落
Concerning my younger sister's whereabouts
可是他是有名的花花公子
But he is a well-known playboy
不入虎穴，焉得虎子
Don't go into tiger's den, how get tiger cub
虽然我有点怕
Although I have a little to fear
可是为了我妹妹
But for the sake of my younger sister
我也只好这样做了
I also had to do like this
你过两天要上电视了
You led to want for two days up the television
何必去冒这个险呢？
Why the need for emit this insurance?
我想愈快愈好
I think to be the quicker the better
淑文…
Shu text …
来了…
Come …
开门呀
Open the door
等一下
Wait for a second
淑文…
Shu text …
等一等
Wait a minute
好了没有？
Like have no?
等一等
Wait a minute
什么事？
What matter?
准备好了没有？
Have already got ready?
时间就快到了
Time shalls arrive soon
马上就好，马上就好
Right away good, right away good
只许成功，不许失败
Allows success and forbid failure
我知道
I know
露露，你跟淑文在搞什么鬼？
The dew exposes, what ghost are you making with Shu text?
这你管不着了
This your tube not wears
我不是说过吗
Haven't I already said
抢来的东西，早晚会被人抢走的
Thing of robbing will be rent away sooner or later
这是上帝的安排
This is the god's arrangement
去你的
Go to you
等着瞧吧
Wait to see
白蒂，又想打架了？
White Di, and then want to fight?
我走了
I walked
我跟你去
I go to with you
不行，不是一个人
Doing not go isn't a person
怕他不肯见
Afraid that he isn't willing to see
没关系，我在远处看着
It doesn't matter, I looking at in the distance
一有事情我就出来救你
An occupy I come out to save you
这样就可以了
So all right
不行，陈太太在外面
Don't go, Mrs. Chen is in the outside
快进去，快进去
Go in quickly, go in quickly
什么事呀？
What matter ah?
快
Quick
什么事呀？
What matter ah?
你们两个干什么？
You what are twos dry?
没什么
Nothing important
我是说她的衣服很好看
I am to say her clothes are good-looking
淑文，你打扮成这个样子
Shu text, you disguise as this appearance
究竟要到哪儿去呀？
Actually want to go to where?
要去勾引George
Want to seduce George
尤小姐，他是我的，你小心点
Ms. You, he is mine, you carefully order
想不到你也跟那个佐治搭上了
Surprisingly you also with that Zuo cure to take ascend
不，不是的
Not, not yes
我怀疑是他把我妹妹拐到香港来的
I doubt is that he turns my younger sister to Hong Kong to come
所以我去查查
So I check
对不起，我去拿点东西
Execuse me, I take some thing
怎么办？时间就快到了呀
How to do?Time shalls arrive soon
真倒霉
True unlucky
她还在外面，怎么办呢？
She still just outside, how do?
怎么办呢？
How to do?
有了
Have
穿我的衣服
Wear my clothes
这怎么行？
How does this go?
我去拿妈妈的头套
I take the mother's head set
这怎么行呀？已经露出马脚了
How does this go?Have already exposed
遮着脚的，有了
Hide feet of and had
穿这条裤子
Wear this pants
现在先冒充Winnie一下
Now pretend to be Winnie first once
她走路是边走边跳的
Her walking is to walk while jumping
怎么跳呀？
How to jump?
你们要出去呀？
Do you want to go out?
是的，Winnie，快点
Yes, Winnie, hurry
Winnie，这个月的房租
Winnie, the rent in this month
今天晚上一定要给我
The tonight must give me
是的
Yes
Winnie，我托你买的唱片
Winnie, I give the record that you buy
不要忘记了
Don't forget
Okay
怎么声音都变了？
How orotund all change?
是女人病嘛
Is woman's disease
我们出去了，拜拜
We went out, religious festival
Winnie，怎么会那么高呢？
Winnie, how can so high?
她穿的是四寸高跟鞋
What she wore is four inch high-heeled shoeses
你快去换件衣服
You change a clothes quickly
我在楼下等你
I wait you in the down stairs
珍妮，干什么？
Jenny, dry what?
没什么
Nothing important
奇怪，好像是Winnie的声音
Strange, seem Winnie voice
到底怎么回事？
Exactly and what is the row?
你们干什么呀？
You are dry what ah?
妈妈，Winnie，我求求你
Mother, Winnie, I beg you
陈太太，你快来
Mrs. Chen, you come quickly
又有人在偷我们东西了
And then someone at steal our thing
快，快
Quickly, quick
你快来看
You see quickly
又来了，真不要脸
Again come, true shameless
你们简直无法无天
You absolutely completely lawless and godless
这次我绝不放过你们
I in no case pass you this time
狂人，色狼，性变态
Madman, sex maniac, sex abnormal condition
为什么一天到晚
Why all day
偷人家的内衣三角裤
Have an affair with man the underwear panties of house
真不要脸，真不要脸
True shameless, true shameless
快点下来道歉
Hurry down apology
要不然的话，我就报告警察局了
Otherwise of words, I reported a police station
你们在胡说些什么？
What are you some in the blah?
我是个老学者
I am an old scholar
下次你们再敢胡乱赖人
You dare be confused again to depend on a person next time
我就你们要赔偿我的名誉
I you have to compensate my reputation
这是什么？
What is this ?
这是讯号旗
This is the signal ensign
绿旗呢是积极进攻
What about green ensign is aggressive to take the offensive
红旗是危险的讯号
The red flag is a dangerous signal
我要你跑的时候
While wanting you to run I
我就拼命的摇动红旗
I try very hard to of wave red flag
好的
Good of
欢迎…
Welcome …
你好
How do you do
我等了你很久了，请坐…
I waited you for a long time, please sit down …
你们进去
You go in
请抽烟
Please smoke
谢谢
Thank
怎么啦？
How?
没关系
Don't relate to
喝杯酒
Drink cup wine
喝杯酒吧
Drink cup bar
不，我不会喝酒的
Not, I can't drink
今天晚上我们去跳舞好吗？
Tonight we dance good?
不，我们还是先谈谈合同的事吧
Not, let's still discuss the business of contract first
只要你答应
Want ～only you promise
我可以付出任何代价
I can pay to serve as what price
我想唱台湾的一首歌
I want to sing a song of Taiwan
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
Lulu好像也唱过这首歌的
Lulu seemed to be also to once sing this song
这首歌很受欢迎
This song is greatly popular
听说是你从台湾找来的
Hear is that you sought to come from Taiwan
那我记不起来了
That I record not to get up
来，喝杯酒吧
Come, drink cup bar
你刚让白蒂代替了Lulu
You just made the white Di replaced Lulu
现在我又插进来
I put to come in again now
不太好意思吧？
Not so good meaning?
那有什么不好意思的
That has what ashamed
老实说
Frankly speaking
白蒂的歌实在是不好听
The song of white Di really isn't good to listen
我只是暂时让她应付而已
I just temporarily make her cope with
因为她常跟我在一块
Because she often heel I at a piece of
我都是赢钱的
I am to win money
听说三个月以前
Hear three months ago
是不是从台湾来了一位歌星？
BE come to a singer from Taiwan?
那我不大清楚
That I ain't greatly clear
我们还是谈谈今天晚上的节目
We still discuss tonight's program
还有合同
Still have contract
老实告诉我
The honesty tells me
你是不是喜欢台湾来的小姐？
Do you like the young lady whom Taiwan comes?
这个跟合同有什么关系？
What relation does this have with contract?
人家说你是有名的花花公子
The somebody else says that you are a well-known playboy
以前我是喜欢常常换女人的
Before I was usually to like to change chemisette
可是我见了你以后呢
But I saw you later
我是真正的爱上了你了
I am to really fall in love with you
你骗我的，我不相信
You cheat mine, I don't believe
尤小姐
Ms. You
真的，我有生以来
True of, I am from birth
第一次闹真正的恋爱
Make real in love for the first time
我爱你
I love you
真的？
Really?
喝一杯
Drink one cup
我们还是谈谈
We still discuss
从台湾来的那位歌星吧
The singer who comes from Taiwan
你是说哪位台湾歌星？
Are you to say which Taiwanese singer?
尤淑慧
You Shu Hui
你跟她认识？
Do you know with her?
不，我是听Lulu说的
Not, I am to listen to what Lulu say
她死了
She died
她嗓子哑了，跳海自杀
She is throat is hoarse and jump into sea a suicide
真的？
Really?
这种人真傻
This kind of person is true silly
喝吧
Drink
你很能喝嘛
You can drink very much
来，再来一杯
Come, come to one cup again
尤小姐
Ms. You
我一直在想找一位理想对象
I always at want to seek an ideal object
现在我总算是找到了
Now I on the whole is find out
快，尤小姐
Quickly, Ms. You
快…
Quick …
什么人开玩笑？
What person play trick?
老板…
Boss …
快去追…快点追回来
Make track for quickly …quickly catch up with
淑慧
Shu Hui
你为什么要死？为什么要死？
Why do you want to die?Why to want to die?
你那么活泼，那么可爱
You are so cheery, so lovely
你真傻
You are true silly
白蒂…
White Di …
还没回来，你就快被人赶走了
Haven't come back, you were quickly kicked out
你又喝醉了？
Do you get drunk again?
活该
What a suck
珍妮
Jenny
珍妮买东西去了
Jenny bought thing to go
珍妮…
Jenny …
珍妮
Jenny
我把一切的希望都寄托在你的身上
I consign the whole hopes all on you
你不要像我
You don't want to be like me
阿姨，我不是Jenny
Aunt, I ain't Jenny
你不是Jenny，是谁呀？
You aren't Jenny, is who ah?
哪来的男人？
Which come of man?
我很久没有被男人抱到床上了
I have already been not embraced a bed by the man to ascend for a long time
佐治，你好狠心
The Zuo cures, you are very cruel
我就知道你忘不了我
I know you are unforgettable I
你回到我身边来了
You return to I came
佐治，你站着干嘛
The Zuo cures, you stand why
佐治
The Zuo cures
你不要这样嘛
You don't want so
我知道你很爱我，我也爱你
I know that you love me very much, I also love you
Jenny…
Jenny …
不…
Not …
Jenny…
Jenny …
Jenny，快回来
Jenny come back quickly
Tommy
怎么啦？Lulu
How?Lulu
你跟Tommy到底做了什么事情？
What affair did your heel Tommy exactly do?
说呀
Say
我醉了，一点也不知道
I am got drunk, at 1:00 also not know
Tommy
到底是怎么回事？
Exactly and what is the row?
老实的说出来，说出来
Speaking of honesty speaks
阿姨把我看成佐治
Aunt sees me as the Zuo curing
给珍妮看见了
Let Jenny see
怎么回事？
What is the row?
珍妮出走了
Jenny fled
出走了
Flee
都是我错
Is all that I am wrong
找不到珍妮
Can not find Jenny
我这一生的希望就完了
I this hope that is life over
好，我去找她回来
Like, I seek she comes back
Tommy，你到哪儿去？
Tommy, where do you arrive?
回来，快点回来
Come back, hurry back
Lulu，都是你
Lulu is all you
给男人迷得神魂颠倒
Be fond of for man heart in torment
这不能全都怪Lulu
All strange Lulu there in no
全怪佐治不好
Whole strange Zuos cure not good
不要这样伤心了
Don't be so sad
别哭了
Don't cry
美雅公寓，是谭经理
The beautiful graceful apartment is manager Tan
淑文，是找你的电话
Shu text, is seek you of telephone
找我？
Seek me?
喂，什么事嘛？
Feed, what matter?
我呀找你当然有事情
I ah seek you to certainly occupy
我要告诉你一个消息
I want to tell you a news
那个佐治不是个好东西
That Zuo's curing isn't a good thing
你妹妹给他害死了
Your younger sister harmed for him to die
他骗你妹妹说
He cheats your younger sister to say
到香港就跟她结婚的
Get to Hong Kong and then get married with her
可是到香港
But get to Hong Kong
你妹妹发现他是个大坏蛋
Your younger sister discovers that he is a big bad egg
气不过就跑去自杀了
Spirit however run to commit suicide
淑文，你不要理佐治这种坏人
Shu text, you take no notice of Zuo to cure this kind of bad person
我恨他，两个都不要
I hate him, none of 2 wants
怎么啦？
How?
你的脸色这么难看
You of the facial expression is so difficult to see
我妹妹被佐治逼得自杀了
My younger sister is cured by the Zuo to force commit suicide
又是那个坏蛋
Is that bad egg again
这个人真可怕
This person is barf city
害完一个又一个
Finish harming one and other
不知道害了多少女人
Don't know to harm how much woman
是呀…
BE ah …
像这种人应该好好的对付
Being like this kind of person should thoroughly deal with
对…
Rightness …
淑文，别难过了
Shu text didn't be sad
淑文…
Shu text …
好，淑慧，我要替你报仇
Like, Shu Hui, I want to revenge for you
好久不来了，你好
Don't come for a long time, you good
最近忙一点
Recent a little bit more busy
你随便坐
You sit wherever you like
淑文
Shu text
尤小姐，里面坐
Ms. You, in sit
谢谢你打电话通知我
Thank you to make a phone call to notify me
老板在吗？
Boss at?
就在里面
At in
尤小姐，你…
Ms. You, you …
尤小姐，你来了
Ms. You, you came
为什么昨天一下子你就不见了
Why were you missing a while yesterday
你还说呢，差点把我吓死了
Do you still say and almost frightenned to death me
我可以在你的夜总会演唱吗？
I can at you of does the night club sing on stage?
当然可以了
Certainly
来，请坐
Come, Please sit down
不过打烊之后
However after closing
我跟你到丽池酒店去谈谈
I arrive a beautiful pond cabaret to discuss with you
我已经订好了101号房
I have already ordered to like No.101 building
地方不错的
The place is quite good
好的
Good of
夜阑人静了，月亮在树梢
Be getting quieter in the dead of night, the moon is in the treetop
爱人你在哪里？
Love you where?
不要忘记了今宵
Don't forget tonight
风吹树影摇
The breeze blows a tree shadow to shake
她唱功不错
She sings an achievement quite good
比白蒂唱得好
Compare white Di to sing well
请里面坐
Please in sit
爱人你在哪里
Love you where
不要忘记了口哨
Don't forget whistle
佐治，这是什么意思？
The Zuo cures, is this what mean?
这里的歌星只有我一个
The singer here only has I 1
不错，只有一个
Quite good, only 1
但是不是你，是她
But isn't you, is her
那么我呢？
So I?
你只要陪我玩牌
You only accompany me to play a card
照样给你薪水
As usual give you the salary
你的口哨被风传来了
You of the whistle was spread by the breeze
我向你招手微笑
I beckon with the hand a smile toward you
禁不住心儿乱跳
Forbid not to live heart son to jump in disorder
风吹树影摇，等你太心焦
The breeze blows a tree shadow to shake and wait you too anxious
爱人你在哪里？
Love you where?
不要忘记了口哨
Don't forget whistle
投在你怀抱，静静地呼叫
The hurl embraces in your bosom, quietly call
深夜静俏俏
The dead hour calms down Qiao Qiao
我俩陶醉在今宵
Two of uses infatuate with in tonight
请进
Just come in
王先生
Mr. Wang
尤小姐
Ms. You
陈太太告诉我你来了此地
Mrs. Chen tells me that you came this place
你来这儿的目的
You come to the purpose here
是不是找佐治算帐？
Seek Zuo to cure to do accounts?
谭逊把一切都告诉我了
Tan Xun tells everything all I
我妹妹是被佐治骗了以后
My younger sister was cured by the Zuo to cheat hereafter
才逼得自杀的
Just force suicide of
所以我一定要替妹妹报仇
So I must revenge for the younger sister
可是他是有名的花花公子
But he is a well-known playboy
你要小心
You want caution
明天上电视，记得吗？
Tomorrow ascend television, remember?
妹妹都死了
The younger sisters all died
上电视还有什么用？
Last the television still has what use?
可是人家已经安排好了
But the somebody else have already arranged
你不去怎么行呀？
Don't you go how to go?
好吧，那我唱一支歌追悼她
All right, that I sing a song to mourn her
勾引了老板
Seduced a boss
又拉个小白脸进来
Pull a small white face to come in again
你倒很有办法
You pour to have much of a way
你不要胡说
You don't want blah
好了好了，不要理她，你走吧
Like like, take no notice of her, you leave
好，我走
Like, I walk
你自己小心呀
Your caution
好
Good
你抢了我的工作
You robbed my work
这都是露露的阴谋
All of this are the scheme that exposes a dew
她是强盗，你又何必做她的帮凶
She is a robber, you why the need for do her accomplice again
你来得正好，我正要找你呢
You come at the right moment, am I about to seek you
这一切都不是露露的错
None of all theses is a dew dew of wrong
她拼了命让Jenny读书
She tried very hard to make Jenny studied
这一切的错都在佐治一个人身上
All these of wrong all cure one personal body in the Zuo up
怎么？你已经开始骂佐治了
How?You have already started scolding Zuo to cure
我去告诉他
I tell him
请吧，你知道吗？
Please, do you know?
我妹妹就是被佐治骗了以后
My younger sister is cured by the Zuo to cheat hereafter
才逼得她自杀的
Just force she commits suicide
跟你一样都是佐治的牺牲品
I am similar to you to is all sacrifice article that the Zuo cures
不，他是真心爱我的
Not, he is sincerely to love my
你看，这是证据
You see, this is the proof
证据？
Proof?
听说有你在他就赢钱
Hear to have you to win money at him
他讨好你，完全是为了想要赢钱
He tries to please you, completely for winning money at wanting
现在就算我退出
Now calculate I withdraw
他也不会回到你身边呢
Can't he returns to you, either
我告诉你，这是他一贯的作风
I tell you, this is his consistent style
喜新厌旧，玩一个扔一个
Like the new and dislike the old, play 1 to throw 1
我受骗了，这家伙
I cheated, this guy
今天早上我们在公寓谈起过
We once started to talk about in the apartment this morning
像佐治这种人
Be like Zuo to cure this kind of person
就应该给他一顿教训
Should give him 1 to teach
白蒂，你我都是女人
White Di, you I am a woman
迟早会被他玩腻了，抛弃的
Sooner or later will be been tired of playing by him, abandon
尤小姐，要是你相信我的话
Ms. You, if you believe me
就该了解我对你一番心意
Should understand me to your some kind of intentionses
你说你怎么样报答我嘛？
You say you how recompense me?
你对我这么好
You are so good to me
我对你要重新估计
I want to re- estimate to you
今天晚上…
Tonight …
带我去开房间
Take I open room
在哪儿呢？
Where?
丽池酒店一零一号房
Beautiful pond cabaret No.101 building
你先去等着，记着要关灯
You go first etc. and record and turn off a light
不关灯，我可不来
Don't turn off a light, I can be not
今天晚上，我可要…
Tonight, I can want …
老兄，最近很少看见你
You hardly sees you recently
在忙什么？
At what's the hurry?
没忙什么，还不是老样子
Have no what's the hurry, not just old appearance
以后呢
Later
还要请你们两位多多的来捧场
Still need to invite you 2 much and much pay tribute
哪里，哪里，太客气了
Where, where, very kind
我告诉你
I tell you
有一天晚上我跟老吴…
One day in the evening I heel old Wu …
对不起，老板，尤小姐给你的
Execuse me, boss, Ms. You gives you
（我先去等你，淑文）
(I go first to wait you, Shu text)
请进
Just come in
出去吧
Go out
是
BE
你是谁？
Who are you ?
是你
Is you
老板
Boss
你这个混蛋
Your this bastard
混蛋
Bastard
Tommy，Tommy
Tommy, Tommy
你一早上到哪儿去了？
You up arrive early in the morning where go to?
孩子
Kid
找珍妮去了
Seek Jenny to go
你，Tommy
You, Tommy
Jenny找到了没有？
Has Jenny been already found out?
没有
Have no
不要再管珍妮的事了
The business that don't want to take care of Jenny again
你要是再去找她我可不答应
If you seek her again, I don't promise
为什么？我为什么不能找珍妮？
Why?Why can I not seek Jenny?
你竟敢对妈咪说这种话
You unexpectedly dare say this kind of words to the mummy
我喜欢珍妮
I like Jenny
孩子，你还早呢
Kid, are you it's yet early
以后我不许你再去跟珍妮多说话
Hereafter I forbid you again go to and much talk with Jenny
不行，你老把我关在笼子里
Don't go, you are old to close me at the cage of son in
我今年已经十八岁了
I have been 18 years old this year
用不着你来管我了
Needless you to take care of me
今天我无论如何
Today I am anyway
一定要把珍妮找回来
Must seek Jenny back
Tommy
等一等，Tommy
Wait a minute, Tommy
你们看，我养了他这么大
You see, I kept him so big
他还是第一次反抗我
He still resists me for the first time
第一次反抗我
Resist me for the first time
好呀，露露
Good ah, dew dew
你给我听着
You let me listen to
你现在给我搬出去
You move away for me now
你马上给我搬出去
You move away for me right away
这样不大公平吧？
So not the archduke is even?
什么？
What?
你不是常说，男人最坏
You are to often say, the man is the worst
露露跟我都是玩具
Dew dew and I am a toy
错的是佐治陈一个人
Wrong is the Zuo cures Chen Yi Ge person
你不能怪露露
You not the ability strange dew expose
我呀实在想不通
I ah really think impassability
她会帮露露说好话
She will put in a good word for dew dew
大概是同病相怜吧
Probably is fellow sufferers understand each other
睡吧
Sleep
Tommy
这么晚了到哪儿去？
So late arrive where go to?
我跟妈妈吵架跑出来了
I fought to rush out with mother
吵架
Fight
你要不要知道到珍妮那儿去呀？
Do you want to know that Jenny goes there?
你知道珍妮在哪里？
Do you know where Jenny is?
知道
Know
暂时不要告诉她们
Temporarily don't tell them
昨天晚上我在这儿碰见她
I ran into her here last night
今天早上把你的情形告诉她了
The situation that made you telling she this morning
她不再误会你了
She no longer misunderstood you
她现在在我的酒吧里
She is in my bar now
要不要去找她？
Want to seek her?
好的，你马上带我去
Okay, you take right away I go to
好
Good
Hi，Nancy
Hi, Nancy
你们看谁来呢？
Who do you see to come?
Jenny，你看
Jenny, you see
Tommy
Jenny
Tommy…
Tommy …
这是莎莉，珍妮暂时住在她家里
This is a kind of insect Li, Jenny temporarily lives in her home
对不起，打搅你了
Disturb you execuse me
哪里
Where
她对我很好，我们成了好朋友了
She is very good to me, we have already become a good friend
有困难的时候
When having is difficult
应该互相帮忙的嘛
Should help each other
谢谢你
Thank you
不要客气
Feel at home
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
虽然大小快慢不一般
Although all of the rate of speed aren't general
只要方向靠得准
Want ～only a direction depend quasi-
自然送你到彼岸
Send you to the other shore naturally
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
永远上下起伏波涛泛
Up and down rise and fall big waves to be suffused with forever
只要船儿把得稳
Want ～only ship son chase steady
顺着风儿一片帆
Follow the breeze son one Fan
纵然遇到狂风和巨浪
Even if meet strong breeze and billow
不用惊怕不用慌
Need not fear need not panic
挺起胸膛往前闯
Rush before sticking out the chest to
莎莉
A kind of insect Li
人生人生就像一条船
The life life is like a ship
淑文唱得真好
The Shu text sings really goodly
我听Nancy说
I listen to the Nancy saying
她的妹妹死了，真可怜
Her younger sister died, poor soul
莎莉，怎么啦？
A kind of insect Li, how?
我在泡茶
I at make tea
我没有钱用了
I had no money to use
今天晚上带吴先生到赌场来吧
Take Mr. Wu to casino to come tonight
我也带George去
I also take George
可是可以
But can
不过这次我一定要拿十个percent
However I must take ten percents this time
如果赢了，我负责替你拿
If win, I was responsible for taking for you
信号还是跟上次的一样
The signal still keeps up with a time of similar
Okay
尤小姐
Ms. You
进来要先敲门，一点礼貌都没有
Come in and knock on door first, a little manner all has no
你才没有礼貌呢
Are you just ill-mannered
昨天晚上是怎么弄的嘛
Last night is how make
你把我害得好苦
You harm me well bitterness
真是对不起
Is really sorry
我把房间号码给弄错了
I give°ed the room number to get mistake
你看看我的脸
You see my face
这个地方我实在是呆不下去了
This place I am really foolish don't descend to go to
尤小姐，你的歌唱得那么好
Ms. You, you of sing so good
除了这儿之外
In addition to here outside
你哪儿都可以去唱的
Where could you sing
我们结了婚之后
After we got married
凭我的关系，我一定会把你捧红的
With my relation, I will definitely hold you red
你听我的话
You listen to my words
那真是太好了
That was really too good
不过做什么事都要用钱的
However do what matters want all to spend money
你有没有钱呀？
Do you have money?
钱好解决嘛
Money like solution
你跟我好一下
You with I is very once
好，来，来嘛
Like, come, come
谭逊
Tan Xun
老板
Boss
你又在花言巧语的是吗？
You and then in the deceiving words of BE?
还不快点给我滚出去
Still don't hurry to roll for me to go out
你不说我也会走的
You don't say that I will also walk
你神气什么？
What are you proud?
我们走着瞧好了
We play by ear
滚
Roll
胆子倒不小
The courage pours not small
竟敢勾引我的女朋友
The girl friend that unexpectedly dares to seduce me
淑文，你太不像话
Shu text, you are beyond the limit
昨天晚上你是怎么搞的？
Were you to how make last night?
怎么搞的？你还说呢
How to make of?Do you still say
昨天晚上我在一一零号房等你
I waited you in the No.11 zero building last night
等了你整夜
Waited your over the night
在一一零号里房等我
On the 11 zeroth in the building wait me
我告诉你是一零一嘛
I tell you is 101
对不起，那是我听错了
Execuse me, that is that I listenned to wrong
淑文
Shu text
你为什么老是推三推四的？
Why did you always push three to push four?
我是真心的爱你
I am sincerely to love you
我们明天结婚吧
Let's will get married tomorrow
结婚？
Get married?
可是我要汽车洋房
But I want car ocean building
汽车洋房
Car ocean building
那要不少钱呀？
Does that want not a few money?
那是我最起码的条件
That is I most at least of condition
你们好亲热呀
You are very warm and affectionate
我正在跟老板要汽车洋房呢
I am just wanting car ocean with boss building
哦，汽车洋房
, Car ocean building
这算不了什么嘛
This is nothing
你应该买给她的呀
You should buy to her ah
你倒说得简单
You pour to say in brief
不花你的钱不就行了吗？
Doesn't money that don't spend you go?
不花我的钱？
Don't spend my money?
那你能买到什么东西？
That can you buy to arrive what things?
你可以利用别人的钱嘛
You can make use of the other people's money
你真笨，告诉你吧
You are true stupid, tell you
吴先生跟丁莲正在赌场等你呢
Mr. Wu heel D be the lotus waiting you in the casino
真的？你说得对
Really?You can say that again
淑文，你跟我来
Shu text, you follow me
我让你见识见识我打牌的技术
I make your knowledge experienced the technique that I play cards
汽车洋房
Car ocean building
你不是什么都有了吗？
Were you to have everything?
来了
Come
来了？
Come?
我来介绍，尤小姐
I to introduce, Ms. You
吴先生
Mr. Wu
请随便坐
Please sit wherever you like
钱带来了没有？
Has money been already brought?
我已经叫人把钱送来了
I have already called the person to deliver money
我们赌一场大的
Our wager one is big
看你输还是我输
See you lose still I lose
那一定是你输
That must be that you lose
别那么自信
Don't so self-confidence
赌大的我是从来没输过的
The wager is big of I am to have never lost
我的钱还没有来
My money hasn't come yet
你先借十万块钱给我
You lend° 100,000 dollars me first
要是不能离台结帐，利息加倍
If can not leave a set to ring it up, interest double
没关系，没关系
It doesn't matter, didn't relate to
好，我跟你
Like, my heel you
是不是？我说一定能赢回来
BE be not?I say to definitely win back
你打得真好
You beat really goodly
你的手气转好了
You of the luck turn
我找陈佐治
I seek Chen Zuo to cure
这边
This place
陈先生
Mr. Chen
你怎么现在才来？钱呢？
How do you just come now?What about money?
刚才谭经理拿走了五万块
Just manager Tan took away 50,000 pieces
还留下了这封信
Still left this letter
他妈的，他拿走五万块
His mama of, he takes away 50,000 pieces
（暂借港币伍万元应用）
(Temporarily use Hong Kong dollar 50,000 is applied)
（你出老千之事我会保守秘密）
(You is old thousand of matter I will keep a secret)
简直是敲诈，混蛋
Absolutely is a blackmail, bastard
怎么回事？
What is the row?
老兄，不要这么紧张嘛
You, don't so strain
咱们还是玩牌嘛
We still play a card
好，我就拿我的夜总会
Like, I take my night club
跟你的十万块钱来赌
And you of 100,000 dollars come to wager
啊，夜总会？
, Night club?
对了
To
你不是说过你赌大钱就会赢的吗
You not is once said your wager big money and then will win
来呀，来
Come, come
老兄，你可别后悔
You, you don't regret
将来你会破产的
You will bankrupt in the future
言之过早
Talk it over early
老板…
Boss …
老什么板呀？
Old what plank ah?
回去…
Return to …
尤小姐，你放心
Ms. You, you trust
我一定会赢的
I will definitely win
Ace一对，派牌
Ace is 1 rightness and send a card
三条A
Three As
两对，来…
2 rightnesses come …
好，我就拿我的别墅
Like, I take my villa
再跟你赌十万块钱怎么样？
Again heel your wager 100,000 dollars how?
Okay
Okay…
Okay …
好，一言为定…
Like, reach agreement verbally …
一言为定
Reach agreement verbally
开
Open
FullHouse
打错讯号
Beat a wrong signal
白蒂，你是怎么搞的？
White Di, are you to how make?
为什么打错讯号你？
Why beat a wrong signal you?
打讯号？
Beat a signal?
原来你们是出老千的
Originally you are that one is olds thousand of
不…白蒂你…
Not …white Di you …
完了
Over
你的夜总会跟别墅都输给我了
You of night club and villas all lost to me
你要守信用
You have to keep promise
我赢了…
I won …
他呀就像这样的
He ah be like such
哭起来了
Cry
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
他把全部财产都输光了呀
He lost everything all properties
好极了
Just splendid
要是Tommy回来了那就好了
If Tommy came back that good
珍妮也是的
Jenny also yes
你们两位知不知道
You 2 know not to know
珍妮跟Tommy相爱呢？
Does Jenny love each other with Tommy?
知道，我是赞成他们的
Know, I am to approve their
其实我也并不反对
In fact I also also has no objection to
只是他们年纪太小了
Just their age is too young
所以我才阻止他们来往的
So I just obstruct their friendly intercourse
你为什么硬把他们拆开
You why hard tear open them
逼得他们私奔呢？
Force do they elope?
私奔？
Elope?
不…我是说他们两个先后离家
Not …I am to say their 2 successively leave home
都没有回来嘛
Didn't come back
你知道他们在哪儿嘛？
You know they where?
是啊
Yes
你知不知道，告诉我们
You know not to know and tell us
别再瞒下去了
Stop deceiving next go to
说吧，Nancy
Say, Nancy
那你就全说出来吧
That you all speak
我是知道的
I am knowing
如果你们都同意他们交朋友
If you all agree that they make friend
我就带你们去好了
I take you go to
同意…
Agree …
快带我们去
Take quickly we go to
我也叫德生去
I also call virtuous living
好呀
Good ah
来
Come
妈咪
Mummy
Tommy
珍妮，你在这儿
Jenny, you are here
妈
Mama
你们放心
You trust
她们已经答应
They have already promised
让你们两个做朋友了
Let you 2 made friend
妈咪  妈妈
The mother of the mummy
这是Nancy的朋友
This is the Nancy friend
幸亏有她来照顾我们
Luckily have her to look after us
谢谢你
Thank you
淑慧
Shu Hui
姐姐
Elder sister
你还活着？
You return on the hoof?
姐姐
Elder sister
她妹妹
Her younger sister
我来香港以后才晓得受骗
I come to Hong Kong hereafter just know to cheat
我一气就跳海自杀
I one spirit jump into sea a suicide
后来被人救了起来
Afterwards is saved to get up
我在电视上看见姐姐
I on TV see an elder sister
可是我没有脸去见你，让你着急
But I have no face to see you, make you worried
真对不起你
Really let  you down
没有关系，只要你还活着
Don't relate to, want ～only you return on the hoof
我就高兴了
I am happy
恭喜你们
Congratulate you
谢谢你
Thank you
干什么？
Dry what?
不能够带她走
Can not take she walks
她欠我们的钱
She owes our money
多少钱？
How much ?
一千块
1,000 piece
胡说，只有三百块
Blah, only 300 pieces
不要紧，我来还，我明天送过来
Unimportant, I to return, I will deliver tomorrow
先给钱，后放人
Give first money, put a person behind
我们找警察去
We seek a police
慢点
Slowly
你想打人？
Do you want to hit persons?
我第一次打倒人…
I knocked down a person for the first time …
行啊…
Go …
我又摔倒一个
I fall down 1 again
Tommy，你真行
Tommy, you are really good
珍妮，煮好了，你快吃了
Jenny, cook good, you ate quickly
早点来了，快点吃吧
Came early, hurried to eat
叫Tommy一块过来吃吧
Call Tommy a piece of to come over to eat
好的，今天例外
Okay, today exception
妈咪给你拿
The mummy takes for you
你坐这儿
You sit here
好不好吃？
Very very unpalatable?
好
Good
喂，是的，请等一等
Feed, please wait a minute yes
妈，佐治想找你
Mama, the Zuo cures to want to seek you
找我？
Seek me?
喂
Feed
Lulu，你好吗？
Lulu, are you good?
我现在正需要钱用
I am just needing now money is used
你借点给我好吗？
You lend° point am I good?
我很快就会还给你的
I am very quick and then will return to you
好，那我马上就来
Like, that I come right away
好
Good
到底是怎么回事？
Exactly and what is the row?
佐治穷途末路
The Zuo cures end of the road end of road
打电话来向我借钱
Make a phone call to come to borrow° from me money
马上就来拿了
Come right away to take
你为什么不拒绝他呢？
Why don't you refuse him?
不，我要借给他
Not, I want to lend to him
一定要好好的教训他一顿
Must thoroughly teach him
佐治陈马上就来了
The Zuo cured Chen to come right away
我去叫德生来
I call virtuous living come
好，快点
Like, hurry
佐治
The Zuo cures
大家注意…你们快点出来…
Everyone notices …you quickly come out …
什么事？
What matter?
他找露露借钱
He seeks a dew dew to lend money
谁要来了？
Who be coming?
佐治要来借钱
The Zuo cures to want to lend money
找露露借钱
Seek a dew dew to lend money
这不要脸的
This is shameless
陈太太
Mrs. Chen
这回你一定得放他进来才行
This time you must definitely put he comes in to just go
说的是
What to say BE
陈太太一定要放他进来
Mrs. Chen must put he comes in
陈太太最恨男人
Mrs. Chen hates a man most
她一向都会反对的
She always will oppose
王先生
Mr. Wang
怎么了？这是怎么回事？
How?Is this what is the row?
女人联合起来可不得了
The woman is allied to put together can impending
来了
Come
怎么这么快？
How so quick?
好，让我来对付他
Like, let I to deal with him
你们快躲起来
You hide quickly
是谭经理
Is manager Tan
干嘛？讨厌
Why?Dislike
我又不是来找你的
I again be not to seek you
我来找尤淑文的
I to seek You Shu Wen
淑文小姐在哪儿？
Where is the Shu text young lady ?
谭先生
Mr. Tan
淑文小姐
Shu text young lady
请进来，今天我们特别欢迎男宾
Just come in, we specially welcome a male guest today
请进  是啊
Just come in yes
淑文，我给你带来五万块钱来了
Shu text, I brought you 50,000 dollars to come
那么多人呀
So many people
有什么了不起？
What fantastic?
你不是说结婚要用钱的吗？
You not is say that the matrimony wants to spend money?
谁稀罕，全是偷来的
Who rare, stealing is whole
就算是偷来的，钱可是真的
At last steal of, money is true
佐治他也不敢报警的
The Zuo cures he doesn't dare to report to the police as well
他马上就要到这儿来
He will come here right away
跟你要回去了
Have to return to with you
你说什么？
What do you say?
我说佐治陈
I say that the Zuo cures Chen
谁呀？
Who ah?
当然是你老板
Certainly is your boss
他在哪儿？
Where is he ?
到这里
Get here
那怎么办？
What to do then?
一定是佐治陈
Must be a Zuo to cure Chen
我怎么办？我躲到哪儿呢？
How do I do?Where do I hide?
佐治，请进来
The Zuo cures, please come in
我们已经恭候多时了
We have already waited respectfullly many
请
Please
听说你找Lulu有事
It is said that you seek Lulu to occupy
现在有一个人想要见见你
A person wants to see you now
就是这一位
Is this
老板
Boss
混蛋，快点把钱还给我
Bastard hurries to return money to me
不还…
Don't return …
他就是佐治陈吗？
Is he it the Zuo that cure Chen?
是的，他就是女人的公敌
Yes, he is a chemisette public enemy
快把钱还给我…
Quick return money to me …
给我…
Give me …
你们到底想怎么样嘛？
You how exactly want?
你们想干什么？
Do you want to do what?
求求你们，饶了我们吧
Beg you, Rao we
你们到底想怎么样嘛？
You how exactly want?
来，现在我们开始审判你们两个
Come, we start judging your 2 now
审判？
Judge?
说得对
Can say that again
罪名是屡次引诱，玩弄和遗弃女人
The criminal charges frequently lures and play with and desert a woman
我可以作证
I can testify
我也可以
I can be also
还有我
Still have me
淑慧
Shu Hui
她就是我妹妹
She is my younger sister
你间接杀人，迫害少女投海自尽
You are indirectly homicidal, the persecution young girl hurl sea commits suicide
绝不能够饶他
In no case can Rao he
对
Rightness
我的厉害你知道吧？
My severe you know?
应该判他们死刑
Should judge their death penalty
对，我赞成
To, I approve
让他们两人坐电椅
Let their 2 people sit electric chair
不，上绞刑架
Not, last hanging
绞刑？
Hanging?
我是冤枉的
I am to wrong
还说冤枉？你真该死
Still say wronging?You are really awful
可是我们女人不应该当刽子手呀
But our woman should not be executioner
对了，我们用手打
To, we by hand beat
用脚踢，先把他们两个揍一顿
By foot kick, first they 2 beat
对吧？
To?
好
Good
让我先来教训他
Let me come first to teach him
饶命…
Rao life …
你们大家来搔他痒呢
You to scart his Yang
饶命
Rao life
别让他跑了
Don't make him run
饶了我吧
Rao I
现在你可知道我们女人的厉害了吧
You knew our chemisette badly now
知道了
Know
饶命呀
Rao life
谁说我们女人是弱者
Who say that our woman is a weak
我还以为你们男人很了不起呢
Do I still think that your man is very fantastic
没想到一个个都是窝囊废
Unexpectedly an is all coward
我总算出了这一口气
I on the whole this one breath
我也是
I am also
饶了我吧…
Rao I …
Tommy，你就饶了他吧
Tommy, you Rao he
饶了我吧
Rao I
饶了我呀
Rao I ah
Tommy
我要好好教训他一顿
I am good friends with well and teach him
你听我讲，你听我讲
You listen to I speak, you listen to me speaking
他就是你的爸爸，陈威廉
He is you of father, William Chen
你就是丽 娟？
Are you a beautiful Juan?
亏你还认识我
Kui you still know me
在十五年前，Tommy只有三岁
In 15 year agos, Tommy is only 3 years old
他就抛弃了我
He abandonned me
从那个时候起，我就恨他
Since that time, I hate him
不过无论如何
However anyway
他曾经是我的丈夫
He once was my husband
他害了你们，我也觉得很抱歉
He harmed you, I also felt very sorry
都是我不好
Is all that I ain't good
谭逊，你不要跑
Tan Xun, you don't want to run
老板，不要抢
Boss don't rob
还给我
Return to me
我自己也吃了很多的苦
I also ate a lot of bitternesses by myself
那次以后
That later
我就觉得女人可怜，男人可恶
I feel that the woman has mercy on, the man is damned
到了今天
Arrived today
我觉得男人也怪可怜的
I feel that the man is also pitiful
佐治，你起誓以后不再这样
The Zuo cures, you take an oath hereafter no longer so
我就求求大家饶了你
I begged everyone Rao you
不行，我不能饶他
Don't go, I not ability Rao he
你害妈咪多苦
You harm a mummy many bitternesses
现在用不着你了
Have no call to you now
妈咪有我来照顾
The mummy has me to look after
你赶快走，走
You at once walk and walk
Tommy，Tommy
Tommy, Tommy
你怎么说话
How do you talk
一下子就像个大人一样？
Be like an adult a while?
妈
Mama
Tommy
各位，恭敬不如从命
Each, polite rather obey orders
对不起，各位，我失陪了
Execuse me, each, I took leave
谭逊，不要走
Tan Xun don't walk
把钱还给我，还给我…
Return money to me, return to me …
不要抢…
Don't rob …
不要抢我的钱
Money that don't want to rob me
看这两人的狼狈相
See these 2 people of distress mutually
真是无可救药
Is really incurable
陈太太
Mrs. Chen
什么事？
What matter?
谢谢你把这铁闸拆了吧
Thanked you to dismantle this iron Zha
后面的铁闸也该拆了才公平
The iron Zha of behind should also dismantle just fair
对啊
To
不拆就像坐牢一样
Don't dismantle to be like to serve prison term similar
其实男女之间不想分开的
In fact the men and women's doesn't think to be discrete
男人可怜
The man is pitiful
那你就答应了吧
That you promised
好了…
Good …
我也是这样想
I am to think like this
从明天开始就把它拆了
Have dismantled it since tomorrow
你们也可以带男朋友进来
You can also take boyfriend to come in
好极了
Just splendid
我们是自由的
We are free
男女之间自由恋爱
The men and women's free love
女人万岁
The woman is long live
陈太万岁
Chen is too long live
女子公寓万岁
The woman apartment is long live
来…今天我请客
Come …I pay today
大家喝个痛快
Everyone drinks happy
来…喝酒
Come …drink
请…
Please …
我们好像一对鞋
We look like a rightness of shoe
我们好像一对船
We look like a rightness of ships
好姐妹，好姐妹
Good sister, good sister
永生永世分不开
Forever and ever inseparable
没见到你心里悲
Don't see your in the mind sad
见到了你心开怀
Saw your heart joyful
好姐妹，好姐妹
Good sister, good sister
欢喜是你在一块
Happy is you at a cake of
Winnie，来…坐吧
Winnie, come …sit
记得别人曾说过
Remember the other people once said
姐妹亲爱才相好
The sister is dear to just fond of each other
相依为命不畏难
Depend on each other for life not to awe by difficulty
我们虽然在等待
We although at wait for
不管你多有钱财
No matter you have money more
不管你有怎能耐
No matter you have how ability
好姐妹，好姐妹
Good sister, good sister
有谁有人能爱戴
Have who someone can support
姐姐，妹妹
Elder sister, younger sister
我们是对好姐妹
We is to good sister
WWW.52HALFCD.COM
时代影视论坛 荣誉出品
谢谢收看！再见